My name is Ryan Hanson. I'm one of the
core developers for the KERI Foundation
development team. Presentation today was
about witnesses and watchers and our boot
service in the KERI infrastructure that
we're deploying and making open to the
world. Witnesses and watchers are a key
part of a crucial part of the KERI
ecosystem the way it's designed to be used
and without them there's some value in key
management at least in terms of being able
to have somewhat self-sovereign keys but
without the witness and watcher
infrastructure to prove that those things
are still valid, that your keys are still
yours, the kind of the whole principle
underlying what KERI is all about falls
apart. For me personally when I first got
introduced to KERI, the witness and
watcher idea was the thing that really
hooked me in because it doesn't really
matter what assertion is made if there's
not something that can prove that that
assertion is true, then it ultimately
doesn't matter. So in practice the witness
and watcher network infrastructure is
critical
for being able to assert and prove that
something is true and therefore to make
the KERI ecosystem actually work. through
through through through through through
Thank you.